artistwebsites.com 2015-03-15

# Terms of Use - Artist Websites

List of Terms and Policies

Effective March 15th, 2014

## Information Collected from Sellers

After opening an account with Artist Websites, a seller is able to create a public profile page and upload information and content to the page include, but not limited to, the seller's name, contact information, biography, headshot, images, hometown, and more. All of this information is fully disclosed on the Artist Websites website. Any site visitor that visits Artist Websites and navigates to the seller's profile page will be able to view all of the public profile information that has been entered by the seller.

## Credit Cards

For any transactions on Artist Websites which require a credit card or debit card, Artist Websites stores the last four digits of the credit/debit card number, the expiration date, and the buyer's name. We do NOT store the full credit card number, pin number, CVV2 number, or any full-track data.

## Security

Artist Websites member accounts, including both buyers and sellers, are secured by member-created passwords. Artist Websites takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information.

## Use of Cookies

Artist Websites uses cookies to store information about each visitor to our Website.

## Links

Artist Websites contains links to other websites. Artist Websites is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, a visitor should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Artist Websites.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, Artist Websites may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so that they will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. Users are bound by changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

## Contacting Artist Websites

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@fineartamerica.com.
